So do you think
Nero will try to win her back?
This is exciting.
I hope they patch things up
and I hope they'll end up together,
so there'll be a sequel to this story.
Good morning, Florence.
What are you doing here?
Florence, he's been waiting here
for quite some time.
He said you owe him dinner
because in the auction,
he bid a million pesos
for you to cook for him.
Is that true?
Well, I thought
that letting go would be difficult,
but the truth is
I seem to be coping pretty well.
That's good.
You act like I'm the only broken-hearted one.
What about you?
I can't believe that girl.
The audacity to show herself to us
after what she did to Florence.
She's using her charms again to trap Owen.
Lina, girl,
why don't you keep an eye on Owen?
I think you two will be perfect together.
Yes.
What I'm saying is,
do you agree to set me up with Owen?
Is it bad?
Is it prohibited?
We don't have a relationship.
You're right.
Maybe I should be dating someone else.
Now, get some mangoes
so we'll have something for dessert later.
Okay, which one?
Is this okay?
No, that's not good. It has patches.
Get the other one.
- This one?
- No, not that one.
The other one.
That one.
Nero!
- Ouch...
- You can't walk with that?
I can.
- Just wait.
- We need to get out of here.
- Ouch.
- Wait.
- Just take it slow.
- Ouch, wait.
We're getting soaked already.
Ouch, wait.
Wait...
There you go.
Are you okay now?
I'm okay now.
Well...
are you okay?
Are you asking if Florence and I are okay?
Obviously, you're still at the losing end.
It looks like my only daughter
is still fuming mad at you.
Well, a bit.
I thought we were doing okay earlier,
because we were slowly
going back to what we were before.
But things suddenly changed.
I'm getting a bit confused already.
I don't understand if I did something bad
or said something wrong.
What did he do wrong?
Did he say something wrong?
Nothing really, Mother.
The truth is, earlier,
we were starting to be okay,
but for no apparent reason,
I suddenly got annoyed with him.
I suddenly became mad.
Maybe I still haven't forgotten
what he did to me, Mother.
He made me look like a fool.
You know, to tell you the truth...
when I found out
that you broke my daughter's heart,
I wanted to crush you.
But when we saw you earlier...
When you dared to face us,
you humbled yourself.
I said to myself, maybe this guy is okay.
You are still young,
that's why you made a mistake.
It's not that I'm pushing, Florence.
The truth is,
I don't like those boy-girl things.
But if you're saying Nero is at fault,
then you're a little wrong.
Mother, why am I at fault?
No, I'm not saying you're at fault.
What I'm saying is,
you should be true to what you're feeling.
The problem with you both
is you became cowards.
You became cowards to say
what you're feeling for each other.
That's how love is.
You should express it.
You should express it in words and actions.
Just like me and my wife.
If only we can say "I love you" every day.
Wait, when was the last time I said
"I love you" to Lydia?
Keep it to yourself.
Florence, the greatest love stories
are the things you talk about.
The ones you write in love letters,
they sometimes become poems.
Let me ask you.
Have you tried to sit in front of Nero,
and stare into his eyes
and tell him what's inside your heart?
Have you told her
everything you feel deep inside?
Were you sincere?
Maybe that's what you need.
You need a chance to talk
sincerely and thoroughly,
so you can fix your misunderstanding.
Lina?
Wait, come on.
Is it true that there's something
between you and Troy?
Oh my God.
This is a surprise.
Are we missing an episode in your life?
Because we're not prepared
for this kind of revelation.
We didn't mean it.
Girl, I've just realized
that you have some secret moves...
In fairness, your moves are so suave.
- Yeah, girl.
- I thought your bullying days are over.
You're picking on me again.
Hey, you're so sensitive.
Yes, can't you take a joke?
Is that why you were
throwing a tantrum earlier?
I'm just annoyed because
should I take the initiative
between the two of us?
Girl, today is all about girl power.
So, if Troy refuses to make a move,
why not you make a move?
This is a queen's gambit era.
Take the initiative.
The powerful queen's opening
until it's checkmate.
Sometimes, I have no idea about
Camille's pop culture reference,
but I totally get her.
- Yeah.
- I totally agree with her.
So what are you waiting for?
What's your opening move?
So what are you afraid of?
If you really like her, go for it.
You're the most talkative among us.
Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?
It's not that easy.
Are you gossiping about me?
No, Grandfather.
It's just girl problems, Grandfather.
And with the look on your faces,
it seems like it's Troy who has a problem.
This is nothing, Grandfather.
Don't worry about me.
I can manage this. I'm okay.
Are you really okay?
I think what you're experiencing right now
is the crippling fear of rejection.
That's what we're all scared of,
to find someone you love dearly,
but doesn't love you.
Will it hurt if you open your heart
and give everything,
and then she doesn't love you?
Of course, it will hurt, very bad!
Ouch, it hurts so much.
But it's not the worst thing in the world.
The worst thing in the world is regret.
Going on living not knowing
what could have been.
I'm giving you all these opportunities,
not because I want to spoil you,
but because I want to give you a chance
to find what you really want.
Because I don't want you
to look back in the past,
thinking about what could've been,
or might have been.
My advice... is don't be scared.
Because for every chance of getting hurt,
is also a chance to find happiness
in this life.
Yeah.
What are you cooking?
Adobo.
It seems you've been cooking
for quite some time.
Isn't it easy to cook adobo?
It depends on the adobo.
There are different ways of cooking it.
Just like this,
I didn't cook it in soy sauce.
Just salt and vinegar.
That's why,
you have to be careful in mixing it
until it releases its own oil.
In short, you're cooking the meat
in its own oil,
but you should always keep an eye on it.
Because you might look away
and it'll be overcooked.
It won't be delicious anymore.
There are things that you can't rush...
or force.
Some things need time and space...
just like us.
The reason why I said what I did,
is because I'm protecting you.
But that's an excuse,
because no matter what I do...
I still hurt you.
I'm hurting the person
who my heart really wants.
Maybe I'm the last person you want to see.
This face reminds you
of all the bad feelings.
I should've given you space and time first.
Don't worry...
I will wait, Florence.
I will wait for you.
There are things that you can't rush...
or force.
Some things need time and space...
just like us.
The reason why I said what I did,
is because I'm protecting you.
But that's an excuse,
because no matter what I do...
I still hurt you.
I'm hurting the person
who my heart really wants.
Maybe I'm the last person you want to see.
This face reminds you
of all the bad feelings.
I should've given you space and time first.
Don't worry.
I will wait, Florence.
I will wait for you.
So what now?
He'll just leave as if nothing happened?
Just like that?
Hey!
Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell,
are you really going to leave
as if nothing happened?
What?
You're leaving, that's just it?
I thought
you were not comfortable with my presence.
That's why I'm going to give you some space.
Space?
Do I look like a rocket ship to you?
Did you even ask me
if that's what I need or that's what I want?
That's what I'm saying.
That's the problem with you.
You assume too much.
Hey!
You're from Gyronella, not from Assumption.
You assume too much
about what I want in my life.
And yes, you're right.
I'm pissed whenever I see you.
Do you know why?
Because I remember what you did to me.
And every time I remember what you did to me,
I want to kick you and crush you
to fine pieces.
But it doesn't mean
that I don't want to see you anymore.
It doesn't mean
that you shouldn't show yourself
and then leave.
And that doesn't mean...
that all my feelings for you
will just go away.
What?
Even if you turn the world upside down,
even if I hit my head there now,
it's still you who my heart wants.
What?
You'll just pretend you don't know?
Don't tell me you didn't hear that clearly.
Are you going
to make me repeat everything, Nero?
I heard everything.
What will you do now?
Will you just stand there? Don't you want it?
Of course, I want.
I can't hear it.
I like you, Florence.
I like you so much!
I like Florence!
Hey, neighbors! Florence has a boyfriend!
I like you.
I like Florence!
Lydia!
- Something is happening outside.
- Huh?
You fools! Why are you tolerating this?
What do you mean kiss?
Nero, Florencia!
Get inside!
We're going to eat now.
Get inside.
- Father...
- Get inside!
Mother.
- Mother!
- Okay.
- Kiss, Father...
- Get inside.
- Father...
I'll kiss you, Mother.
I'm happy with you both
because your feelings for
each other are so connected.
But let me remind you, you're still young.
I will only allow you to have a relationship
if there are rules.
That's right.
Why are you winking?
I'm winking at you because you're sexy.
Don't worry. I respect your wishes.
Very good answer.
First rule.
No kissing.
- What?
- Don't you want that?
No, that's right. Your mother is correct.
- She's right.
- Mother.
Nero and I are not thinking about that.
What do mean you're not thinking about it?
Earlier, the neighbors were egging you,
and you're already game.
Your lips were as long as EDSA.
I agree with mother.
Don't be pressured, Florence.
Mother?
You're calling me Mother that soon?
Wow!
Hey, Nero. I trust you.
Don't ruin my trust in you.
Wait, just to be clear.
So what's allowed?
Kiss on the cheeks?
No, that's not allowed.
That's near the lips.
Kiss on the forehead?
Father, what am I?
Nero's grandchild?
How about... holding hands?
Is that allowed?
Okay.
Kiss on the hand?
Is that allowed?
No.
You can't kiss
until you're the lead character
in your own movie.
Okay, that's enough.
What I know is...
This is a new and beautiful chapter
in our lives.
And we should always celebrate
the new connections...
that we're forming in our journey.
So, Nero...
Welcome to the family.
Welcome.
Cheers.
But a kiss is not allowed.
Nothing. Just holding hands.
Holding hands is allowed while walking.
Are you sleepy already?
I don't know if I'd fall asleep tonight.
Don't be too excited.
I should be excited.
And we're on the way to the exciting part.
Hey, you fool.
Maybe you've forgotten my mother's rules.
You made a promise.
Of course, what I mean is
you're officially part of my world.
Wow, before, you were not talking,
but now, you have remarks like that.
Go ahead and sleep.
Don't I get a good night's kiss?
That's not allowed, remember?
It's not allowed face-to-face,
but they didn't say it's not allowed
over the phone.
Oh my, you already found loopholes
in the rules.
You know, that's the problem
why the Philippines is not progressing.
You always make an alibi
until you get away with it.
- That's the only thing I'm asking.
- Here it is.
What's that?
That's it.
One more, the signal is a bit choppy.
Thank you.
What do you mean thank you?
Are you saying it's just me?
The business will go bankrupt
if that's how you do it.
It's embarrassing.
Oh, so that's it.
If you do it, it's embarrassing,
but if I do it, it's okay.
Okay, I'm just getting ready.
There are no feelings.
Did you close your eyes?
You should close your eyes.
One more time, come on.
One more...
- What's that, 20?
- It's 20.
You're early even though you came home
late last night.
Come on, let's have breakfast.
You cooked, Grandfather?
Well, you know with the attitude
of my grandsons,
no chef stays long with us,
so we just tried to cook.
So there you go. That's the result.
You know, Nero,
even if you don't ask,
your grandfather cooks well.
The next thing he'll be cooking is chopsuey.
Right, Grandfather?
Don't do that again.
It's just a joke.
Just a little push and we'll hire you
as a chef to the Ferells.
Quiet!
What?
Come on, sit down and I'll prepare your food.
No need, Ms. Serafica.
I'm going out for brunch,
so it's okay for me to skip breakfast.
But next time, Grandfather,
I'll eat what you've cooked. Promise.
Brunch? We know you'll be with Florence.
Just give her my kisses.
Me too, give her my hugs and kisses.
Me too, Nero.
Of course, don't forget Mr. Dencio...
- Nero! Us too.
- Us too, Nero...
Smoochie-smooch.
Nero left already.
It's not Nero...
Nero.
- Bye, Mother. Bye, Father.
- We'll go ahead.
Are you laughing at me too?
Of course not.
I'm just imagining
Grandfather Garp, Ma'am Serafica, Mr. Dencio,
Mr. Iking, Mr. James, and Ms. Patotina
pranking you.
It's really funny.
But seriously, Grandfather Garp is cooking?
Yes.
I pity Grandfather Garp.
If only I was still in the mansion.
You know, it looks like he's enjoying it.
And Ms. Serafica is there.
The truth is, we don't really need a cook,
we just got used to someone's cooking.
And it's okay that grandfather is cooking.
It's like he found a new hobby.
With cooking?
- Yes.
- Really?
Well then,
I'll send him more and more recipes,
especially his favorites and yours too.
That's a good idea.
But wait, Nero,
why did you pick me up this early?
What's happening?
Today is the first day
to the road to happiness.
And I'm planning to celebrate that
with the longest date in history.
Really? The longest date in history?
Yes. And I already have plans for that.
We'll go strolling at the park,
we'll watch a movie,
we'll attend a mass in Baclaran Church...
we'll try the rides in the amusement park,
and we'll do sunset watching.
That's a lot.
That's why it's the longest date in history.
And I've prepared everything.
And the first place we're going,
is to have a delicious brunch.
Brunch?
Yes.
Let's go?
Repeat after me.
Let's go, Florence.
Let's go to the longest date in history.
Wow.
We're here again?
- It's the same waiters again?
- Thank you.
Deja vu.
So, is this the start
of the longest date in history?
This is just the start, Florence.
I still have a lot of surprises for you.
Imagine this.
Before, I only watch dates like this on TV,
and now, I'm having a date too.
And I'll be surprised
because there'll be fireworks all of a sudden!
Am I going to see your fireworks?
Sorry.
Let's pretend I won't be surprised.
There are no fireworks, Florence.
But my surprise is more beautiful
than fireworks.
- More beautiful?
- Yes.
A thousand fireworks?
- Or there are no fireworks?
- There's no fireworks.
Okay, go ahead and order pork adobo,
which is 1,000 pesos per meal,
and the soup, which is 450 pesos
with gold dust ingredients.
But let's share, okay?
It's really expensive.
- You said it.
- As long as we share it.
- Let's share.
- Yes, share.
- That's it.
That's all.
Excuse me, I'm so sorry to intrude,
but can I talk to Florence
for a couple of minutes?
What are we going to talk about?
Let's go.
I've been meaning to call you,
but I felt
that I should talk to you in person.
Maybe Nero told you already...
but I just wanted to apologize
for my behavior.
I'm sorry, but...
I can't forgive you for what you've done.
I understand.
No, I'm just joking.
Hey, can't you take a joke?
You're so serious.
That's okay, I already get it.
And my boyfriend can make you
do crazy things.
In fairness to you,
you have a fighting spirit,
but it's still wrong
that you resorted to blackmail.
But it's still an A for effort.
Thank you, Florence.
You know what, the way that I see it,
it's Nero who won the jackpot
in your relationship.
And the way that you call him boyfriend
really has a nice ring to it.
Isn't it awkward to call him boyfriend?
It's my first time.
You're awesome, Florence.
And truly,
I sincerely wish you and Nero happiness.
- Sorry, Nero.
- Thank you.
That's okay.
You also need closure.
Exactly.
If you compare it to
the continuation of a drama series,
that's it.
So, let's eat.
Let's dig in.
Florence!
So, the reason why you left early
is that you have a date.
And I knew it, I'll see you here.
I miss you, but I really need you.
I need your advice, Florence.
Advice?
For what?
I got scared, Florence.
Because it was you
who built my persona in the chat.
Now that I've met her in person,
it seems I've lost my confidence.
I can't stop thinking
that she might think I'm a fake,
or worse, that I'm just interesting online
but very boring in real life.
Troy, just relax.
We're talking about Lina.
And if there's one thing I know about Lina,
she won't judge you.
I'm sure
she'll like
both your exciting and boring parts.
And also, your corny side, always.
Really?
Yes, mark my word.
Do you still need anything?
- I feel better.
- You feel better already?
- You're done?
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Nero,
there are a lot of commercial breaks.
What are we talking about earlier?
Soup?
I'll start eating the soup.
Florence!
What will I do, Florence?
I keep thinking of him...
but ever since he found out it was me,
he's ignoring me and refused to talk to me.
It's like he's a different person.
Or maybe he doesn't find me interesting
in real life?
Maybe I'm more interesting online?
Lina, don't overthink too much.
Maybe he is just waiting
for the right timing.
Really?
I was able to spend a long time
with the Ferells in the mansion.
I became their cook,
that's why I know how they think and move.
And if there's one thing I'm sure about Troy,
he will find you very likable.
I think you're just saying that.
Lina, I am many things,
but you know me, I'm not a liar.
Well, you're right.
So just be patient.
What you're waiting for will come.
But if you can no longer wait,
then take the initiative.
Knock on his heart.
That's what Aira and Camille said.
You can do it.
Just believe in yourself.
I'm so happy I was able to talk to you.
Just knock...
Troy...
Just knock.
You can do it.
Maybe no one will come anymore.
It's too much if someone else arrives.
Let's ask them to reheat the food.
We had them reheat this twice.
Twice?
Twice.
It's still hot.
Let's eat!
So, what were we talking about?
Soup?
Florence Dela Cruz is back!
Yes.
Is there anything else we can do?
Please?
Even if I double the payment?
Okay, fine.
Okay, thank you.
I'm sorry, Nero.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
Let's eat, and then let's go.
Let's carry out your plans
for the longest date in history.
All my reservations were canceled already.
I'm really sorry, Nero.
No, it's okay.
What's important is I was able to be with
the most important person in my life today.
Mr. Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell,
I'd like to thank you for showing me
how big my world is.
Don't be sad anymore.
Go ahead and smile.
Come on, smile...
Smile... Smile.
I know...
What's that?
Copy it.
I don't want to.
Come on, copy it.
Please?
You can do it.
Here.
And stick it...
Stick it.
Mr. Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell...
I love you.
I love you so much.
Ms. Florence Dela Cruz,
I love you so much too.
I love you.
Thank you for today, Nero.
I'm the one who should thank you.
And I can't wait to spend a new day with you.
Oh, go to sleep now.
Good night, my love.
Good night, Love.
Hello?
I thought it's good night already,
why haven't you hung up?
Why haven't you hung up too?
Go ahead and end the call.
You go first.
Okay.
Good night, sweet dreams.
Good night, Nero.
Sweet dreams too.
Hello?
Hey, why are you still there?
End the call.
You go first.
Okay, I'll end the call now,
but tomorrow, it's your turn.
Deal.
Hey, Florencia, end that call.
You and Nero should go to sleep!
Hello?
Florencia, go to sleep!
Why is this happening to me?
I was doing okay.
I'm happy with my life
with my mother and father.
I don't need this complication.
Did I do something wrong?
Did I do something bad
for all this to happen to me?
I noticed the first time I saw Florence
that she looks kind of familiar.
Her parents, Lydia and Federico,
they're in a lot of trouble.
Most likely they'll be accused
that they had something to do
with the death of Alyanna Almero.
What happened? What was their reaction?
Denial.
Looking desperate in their attempt
to stand by their lies.
Look, for all I know,
her fake parents are packing their things now
to take my daughter away.
They can't hide.
I will personally look for her
and drag her back here.